Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Writings, 1954-2014; 4; 12.93 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Advocacy Day, 2002; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, AFI [American Film Institute] Speech for Warren [Beatty], 2008; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, All Saints, 1995-2005; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, An Evening with Jane Fonda at the Paley Center, 2011; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, April 2nd Speech to Philanthropist's Conference in Atlanta, 1995-2005; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Archer School Commencement, 2002; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Atlanta Women's Chamber of Commerce, 2000; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Atlanta Women's Network Luncheon, 2000; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, California Department of Health Services, Office of Family Planning's Leadership 2001 Conference, 16 Mar 2003; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Campaign for Economic Democracy, 1977; 2 folders (Box 71, Folder 27-28)
    Related Materials
    The folder is associated with the following material: Slides, Campaign for Economic Democracy, Series 5, Box 73.
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Chamber of Commerce, 2005; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Changing the Realities of Girls' Lives, approximately 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Chicago Event for Harriet, 22 Apr 2002; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Circle of Hope Fundraiser, Piedmont College, 18 Apr 2000; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, CNN Teen Pregnancy Interview, 2006; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Commencement Speech Emma Willard, 4 June 1989; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Council on Foreign Relations, 12 Nov 1997; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Emma Willard Commencement, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Emory, 2000; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, The Enhancing Family Life Act of 1999, 19 Jan 1999; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, For Troy and Simone, 2006; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, GCAPP, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, GCAPP Program Activities, July 2001; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Georgia Campaign for Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Girls' Incorporated, Girls' Rights Campaign Launch, 15 Oct 1999; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Girls' Inc Speech, Draft, 1995-2010; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Good Housekeeping Questions, 2005; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Grantmakers for Children, 10 Oct 2001; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Growise University of North Carolina, 24 Apr 2000; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Harvard's Graduate School of Education, May 2000; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Jane Fonda GCAPP Roast, 1 June 2006; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Junior League, 1995-2010; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Junior League, Draft 2, 26 Jan 1997; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, L.A.-NOW Tribute to Barbara Streisand, 1984; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, L.A. Press Club, 18 Nov 2012; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Lily Tomlin's Mark Twain Prize, 26 Nov 2003; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, L'Oréal Slogan Celebration, 2011; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Omega "Women & Power" Conference, 10-14 Sep 2004; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Paidea [School], 1995-2010; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Population Affinity Group, Draft 1, Oct 2000; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Press Club Speech, Draft 2, 1998; 1 boxes; 1 Reels (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Refuge House, Oct 2001; 1 boxes (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Sherry Lansing Leadership Award, 2011; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Simmons School of Management: Leadership Conference, 1 May 2004; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Speech to Children of Armenia Fund, NYC, 20 Oct 2006; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, TEDx Session, 1 Dec 2011; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Troup County Family Connections, 29 Apr 1999; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Unique Lives…Denver, 2 June 2003; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, V is for Vote!, 2000-2008; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, [Untitled], 1995-2010; 1 folders (Box 72, Folder 40)
- Photographs, 1964-2003; 5; 0.67 linear feet (2 boxes)
  The Photographs series includes photographs and negatives related to Fonda's adolescent life, professional life, workout series, and family. There are oversize items.
  Separated Materials
  Original audiovisual materials and the one item in a mapcase are off-site and require advanced notice to view. Please contact Special Collections to request these materials in advance and allow up to 48-hours for their arrival.
  - Slides, Campaign for Economic Democracy, 1977; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 73, Folder 1)
    The slides are associated with the following material: Unpublished: Speeches, Campaign for Economic Democracy, Series 4, Box 71.
  - Photographic Prints, 2nd Anniversary of Kent State, 1972; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Prints, 1964-2000; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Photographic Prints, The Brentwood Town and Country School, 2000; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Prints, Emma Willard School, 2003; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Prints, Hirschfeld, Al, Jane Fonda, 1975; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Prints, Introduction to the Enemy, -Negs-, 1973-1974; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Prints, Introduction to the Enemy, Negatives, 1973-1974; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Prints, [Jane Fonda, Ted Turner, and two unknown subjects in graduation regalia,], 1990-2010; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Prints, [Laurel Springs Camp], 1977-2000; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Prints, To Ted Turner and Jane Fonda with best wishes, and thanks for the visit Bill Clinton, 18 May 1995; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Photographic Prints, Workout Photos, 1980-1990; 4 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 11-14)
  - Photographic Prints, Unknown, 1940-2010; 2 Photographic Prints (Box 74, Folder 15-16)
  - 19 x 23 OK to Trim Cream Linen [Henry Fonda, damaged photograph], 1940-2010; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Peter, Henry and Jane Fonda, 1976; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Tony McGrath [?], 8/30, 1940-2010; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Jane Fonda and Eve Ensler, 2000-2010; 1 Photographic Prints (Mapcase 7, Drawer 26)
- Audiovisual materials, 1970-2014; 6; 37.88 linear feet (55 boxes)
  The Audiovisual Materials series is organized into two series: film projects and Interviews/TV. The series includes the following formats:
  1/8" Audio Cassettes
  1/8" Audio Tapes
  1/4" Audio Tapes
  1/2" Audio Tapes
  1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS)
  1/2" Betamax Video Cassettes
  1/2" Sanyo V-60 Video Cassettes
  3/4" U-Matic Video Cassettes
  3/4" U-Matic S Video Cassettes
  1" Video Tapes
  2" Video Tapes
  16 mm film
  35 mm film
  10" LP Vinyl Album
  CDs
  DVDs
  These materials document three aspects of Fonda's life: her political activism, including that related to her anti-Vietnam War efforts; the Jane Fonda Workout series; and interviews and television appearances, featuring Jane Fonda and/or her third husband, Ted Turner. Many of the audiovisual materials related to the Jane Fonda Workout series are on loan to Fonda. The Vietnam-era audiovisual materials are of particular historical value.
  In general, the sub-series are organized chronologically and alphabetically. Many items in each sub-series have related manuscript materials and it is noted within the finding aid.
  There is extensive 16 mm footage related to the 1974 Vietnam-related, anti-war documentary, Introduction to the Enemy. The film elements related to this prpject has been maintained in the order in which it was donated to the Sophia Smith Collection. The titles of each box are listed with the title of each film element. Some boxes contained multiple elements and researchers may find repeating titles. Some box and item titles are in Vietnamese. Introduction to the Enemy, was produced by Jane Fonda, Tom Hayden, Haskell Wexler, Christine Burrill, and Bill Yahraus, filmed and directed by Haskell Wexler, and released through Fonda's production company, I.P.C. Films. The majority of the materials related to Introduction to the Enemy, have been digitized and are available for use by researchers.
  Other film projects include On Golden Pond, Lakota Woman, and Grapes of Wrath.
  There are many copies of interviews and recordings of Jane Fonda on VHS and U-matic tapes.
  Some CDs and DVDs include data, photographs, PowerPoint presentations.
  - Paper manuscripts related to audiovisual materials, approximately 1974-2016; 1 boxes (Box 75)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Reel 1, 1974 October 10; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (wav file) 160D-06 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Tape #1, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-07 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Tape #2, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-08 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Reel 2, 1974 October 10; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-09 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Tunnel, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-10 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Cassette #2 Heroines, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-11 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: #3, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-12 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: #4, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-13 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Message from PR Minister, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-14 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho Interview Sync, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-15 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho Interview, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-16 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Ngaingh Thi, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-17 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: NK Vien Interview, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-18 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: UN Reception #3, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-19 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: UN Reception #2, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-20; 1 items (UN Reception #2, Box 75) (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: UN Reception #1, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/4 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) 160D-21 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-3, Old Lady Interview on Boat Officer in Dark of Boat Transfer to 16 mag, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN3; 1 items (SN Tapes Sound Log, Box 75) (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-4, Tung Quoc AM Interviews Syn, 1974 April 14; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN4 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-5, Actress-Jane Interview, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN5 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-6, Tape #3 Camera Rolls 8+9, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN6 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-7, Short grey hair man talks, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN7 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-8, Jane + Tom listen to grey hair man tell about trip to south EF, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN8 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-9, Roll 1 on leaving Hanoi + some synch [sic] wild tracks in jeep, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN9 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-10, 3rd part Madame Van Trang + Beginning of Buddhist Guy in Robe, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN10 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-11, Tape of morning of April 11, shot 3 rolls eco, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN11 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-12, 1st part Madame Van Trang Interview, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN12 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-13, tape #1 Camera Roll 1-5, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN13 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-15, April 11 +12 Girl Reading Poem at Air Base, Old Man + Girl hero in bushes sync, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN15 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-16, PM Apr. 12, 2 part girl hero in bush, 1st roll collective far, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN16 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-17, Roll 2 Madame Van Trang synch [sic], approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN17 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-18, Interview of Mrs Chi April 9th, Roll #1, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN18 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-22, Hospital-woman Dr. Surgeon at Window, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN22 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-24, Workers (women) very little synch [sic] lots of straw hats + faces + mud, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN24 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: S-26, PRG Part of this tape was recorded with dead batteries, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN26 (Box 76)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: S-27, 2nd day prg am, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN27 (Box 76)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: S-28, Tail out synch [sic] Art Miller Play-3 200 fr EF Rolls, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN28 (Box 76)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: S-31, Medicinal Garden Wounded mine victim + court room, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN31 (Box 76)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: S-32 PRG Meeting #1, approximately 1974; 1 items (1/8 inch audiotape); 1 items (1 wav file) SN32 (Box 76)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, video recording: Thi-sync outs-Pix, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_01 (Reel 70)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Pulled from WKPrint -C.R.Z52 Footage Dark-N.G., approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_80; 1 items (Jane Fonda paperwork, Box 75) (Reel 71)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Out-outs "Tradition", approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_89 (Reel 71)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi Pham Van Dong, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_103 (Reel 73)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: J1/92 64 484 900, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_104 (Reel 74)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy-Sync Pix RI Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_112 (Reel 75)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy-Sync Pix RII Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_113; 1 items (Introduction to the Enemy Pic reel 1B, Box 75) (Reel 76)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Foot R1 "B" "Introduction to the Enemy", approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_114 (Reel 77)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy, 2B Head Cap, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_115; 1 items (2B closed, Box 75) (Reel 78)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: R1 Introduction to the Enemy, I.P.C., Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_116 (Reel 79)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: R2 Introduction to the Enemy, I.P.C. Head Cap, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_117 (Reel 80)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Ha Thinh→ Vinh D-7A, JJ75, I17, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_118 (Reel 81)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Quoc & heroines near water buffalo MOS HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_119 (Reel 82)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Pix PRG lady on red couch, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_142 (Reel 83)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: MOS Buddist [sic], eating, early rising, AITU Village w/ 2 old viets; Patrol-blue room (JJ77), approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_161 (Reel 84)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 2 old viets/Buddhist, Sync outs, PIX HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_167 (Reel 85)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: monk interview, 2 old viets, lady reading poem SYNC PIX, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_168 (Reel 86)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: QUOC-Arthur Miller, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_172 (Reel 87)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Roll EC 81, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_173; 1 items (Negative Inspection, Box 75) (Reel 88)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi w/ Troy + w/ Vien Q 34B/EE64B/EE65-7, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_179 (Reel 89)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi April 1-4 - w/ Tra Siong + Kids-by lake-PRG Embassy-Schools-Wang Tung Ext. Interview-Leaving Troy, sync-Track HEAD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_201 (Reel 90)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi April 1-4 - w/ Tra Siong + Kids-by lake-PRG Embassy-Schools-Wang Tung Ext. Interview-Leaving Troy, sync-Track HEAD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_202 (Reel 91)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi-Movie Studio-Interview w/ Actress-Actress in Print Shop, Sync Pix Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_204 (Reel 92)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Ha Tinh Interview w/ Tung + Quoc Sync Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_206 (Reel 93)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Quoc-Sync Pix HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_207 (Reel 94)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Quoc's Haskell's Joke-PIX, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_208 (Reel 95)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Salt workers-lifts from cut, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_225 (Reel 96)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: 11 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_226 (Reel 97)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_227 (Reel 98)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_228 (Reel 99)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Jo lady doctor/Jane crying in white coat/surgeon interv./garden PIX Sync Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (mov and wav file) FondaFilm_229 (Reel 100)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised trim AA Tra Giang, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_231 (Reel 101)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Camloc women/ARUN Defect-Camloc + Aitu, Sync Outs Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_240 (Reel 102)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, motion picture recording: 4 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (no file) FondaFilm_260 (Reel 103)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Interview w/ Jane & Ngainh Thi (in French); interv. w/ Vien; Sync TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_268 (Reel 104)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Interview w/ Jane & Ngainh Thi (in French); interv. w/ Vien; Sync Pic Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm film); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_269 (Reel 105)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy R2 TRK 10-10-74, 1974 October 10; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_280.2 (Reel 106)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy R2 TRK 10-10-74, 1974 October 10; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_280 (Reel 107)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Sound PRG Lady, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_300 (Reel 108)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: monk interview, 2 old viets, lady reading poem SYNC TRK, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_323 (Reel 109)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: QUOC-Arthur Miller, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_326 (Reel 110)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Cassette-WS-Tunnel + Mr Diet, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_327 (Reel 111)